

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science Multimedia and Animation Technology Mahanakorn University of Technology 2016 - 2018

Diploma in Information
Technology
Intrachai Commercial College
2013 - 2015

SKILLS

- Python
- PySide/PyQt
- PostgreSQL/MySQL
- SQLAlchemy
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- JSON
- Git GitHub/GitLab
- Linux bash/tcsh

LANGUAGES

- Thai
- English

APISIT SENLUANG

Backend Developer

- apisit.senluang@gmail.com
- **4** +66 85-990-2957
- 199/135 The Connect 53, Kanchanaphisek Road., Thap Chang Sub-district, Saphan Sung District, Bangkok 10250.

ABOUT ME

A former 3D Animator who shifted to Pipeline Developer, passionate about technical problem-solving. I'm a quick learner who eagerly enjoys new challenges. My experience working closely with artists and the team has enhanced my communication and collaboration abilities.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pipeline Engineer

2022 - 2024

The Monk Studio Co. Ltd.

My Responsibilities in the Pipeline Engineer Role:

- Data Management: Ingesting, organizing, and packaging files.
- Tools: Building custom tools using Python and PySide2.
- **Database**: Experienced in using PostgreSQL for both direct SQL queries and the SQLAlchemy ORM framework.
- **Maintenance**: Fixing bugs, supporting users, and optimizing systems for efficiency.
- Infrastructure: Collaborating with IT on infrastructure issues.
- DCC Integration: Developing pipelines for DCC software E.g. Maya, RV, Nuke, Houdini, Blender.

3D Animator 2021 - 2022

Lap Production Co. Ltd.

Animate 3D characters and props in Maya. Automate repetitive tasks using Python scripting. Create a simple pipeline for media review and delivery to reduce errors and ensure consistency using Python with PyQt framework.

3D Animator (contract)

2019

World Learning Hub Asia Pacific Co. Ltd.

Create 3D Characters in Character Creator, animate it in iClone and paint textures using Blender